Psi Gamma Sorority and Alumnae Association, Inc.; Records ua801.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Psi Gamma Sorority and Alumnae Association, Inc. Records
1898-1997
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Psi Gamma Sorority and Alumnae Association
ua801.003
12.66 cubic ft.
Psi Gamma was founded in 1898 at the New York State Normal College for Teachers and the Alumnae Association in 1922. The sorority split in 1991 over whether to abandon local status or become a chapter of a national sorority.
Administrative History
On February 15, 1898, Edith Stoneman, Gertrude Hall, and nine other students of the New York State College for Teachers organized the Psi Gamma Sorority. L. Elizabeth Reed became the first president of the sorority and Margaret Mooney of the New York State College English Department became its first sponsor. In 1906 the sorority rented an apartment and soon thereafter moved into a house on Clinton Street where it held its regular meetings for several years ["Psi Gamma Sorority Brochure 1898-1988", p. 6, Anniversary - 90th, Psi Gamma Sorority Subject Files].
On April 29, 1922, twenty-two faculty, alumnae, and active sorority members founded the Alumnae Association ["Minutes of the Alumnae Association of Psi Gamma Sorority", p. 2, Minutes - Annual Meeting and Executive Meeting, Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Subject Files]. Two years later, on February 2, 1924, 16 members of the Alumnae Association signed a Certificate of Incorporation after the motion was made, seconded, and carried during the association's regular meeting ["Minutes", p. 22]. Later that year the association purchased the Lochner house at 1104 Madison Avenue for the active sorority. Three years later the alumnae association sold the Lochner House and purchased the J. Harris Loucks House at 113 South Lake Avenue, where the sorority was housed until 1959 ["Minutes", p. 57-59].
In 1963, the University at Albany, under the leadership of President Even R. Collins, required each Greek organization to sell its house and move into the new residence halls on the main campus ["Memo To Faculty and Students", May 22, 1963, Greek Workshops Folder 1, Psi Gamma Sorority Subject Files]. In spite of widespread student discontent over this new policy, Psi Gamma Sorority moved to Van Rensselaer Hall in 1965 ["Minutes, February 15 1965", Minutes-Regular Meeting 1964-1965, Psi Gamma Sorority Subject Files].
Enrollment in national Greek organizations began to increase in 1976 when the SUNY University Board of Trustees revoked its ban against national fraternities and sororities. In 1991 Psi Gamma held a vote in order to determine whether or not the sorority would also seek a national sponsor. Only one-third of the active members voted to continue Psi Gamma's tradition as a local chapter. The other members separated to form a new chapter of the national Alpha Xi Delta Sorority [Alumnae Newsletter, February 1992, p.2, Alumnae Newsletters 1981-1997, Alumnae Association Subject Files].
In 1991 a group of students at Stony Brook, SUNY, approached the Psi Gamma Sorority seeking admission as a sister sorority. Psi Gamma recognized the new group as the Psi Gamma Sorority Beta Chapter even though such an event was without precedent. The Alumnae Association believed that only it had the right to recognize branch sororities, though it also recognized that changes in its Constitution and Articles of Incorporation were necessary in order to do so ["Alumnae Newsletter, February 1992", p. 2]. In 1993, the association amended these documents and officially adopted the Psi Gamma Sorority at Stony Brook as the Beta Chapter; a sister sorority to the Alpha Chapter in Albany [Alumnae Newsletter, Spring 1994, p. 1, Alumnae Newsletters 1981-1997, Alumnae Association Subject Files].
Scope and Contents
Psi Gamma Sorority Records (1898-1995).
This sub-group contains correspondence, minutes, reports, scrapbooks, photographs, constitutions, by-laws, video and audio cassettes, newspaper articles, membership lists, financial records, and ephemera of the Psi Gamma Sorority. Although the records date from 1898 through 1997, the bulk of the records were created between 1940 and 1995.
Records produced during routine administrative activities include the Psi Gamma Sorority meeting minutes (1955-1994), president's notes (1974-1983), the alumnae secretary reports (1968-1977), the annual reports (1992-1993), and the budget files (1972-1976, 1993-1994), all located in the Subject Files Series. Records that establish guidelines for the governing of the sorority include the constitutions (1965-199?), the executive board handbook (1988-1989), and the Panhellenic Association rules and regulations (1988-1994), all located in the Subject Files Series.
Records relating to sorority sponsored social events can be found in the rush ceremony files (1955-1993), and the anniversary celebration files (1968-1988), all located in the Subject Files Series. Numerous photographs, newspaper articles, and other ephemera commemorating sorority activities are located in the Psi Gamma Scrapbook Collection Series (1898-1995). The Psi Gamma Sorority Ephemera Series (1943-1993) consists of items used in sorority activities such as pledge paddles, banners, clothing, sorority family trees, and tableware. Finally, the names, comments, and addresses of sorority members who attended events such as open houses, conflict parties, and anniversaries are located in the Psi Gamma Sorority Guest Books Series (1948-1991).
Information about sorority membership is located in the membership lists (1933-1994) and the pledge lists (1963-1994), both in the Subject Files Series, the Composite Photographs Series (1951-1952, 1968-1995), and the Psi Gamma Sorority Guest Books Series (1948-1991). Images of sorority members are found in the Annual Scrapbooks (1952-1991), the Anniversary Scrapbooks (1898-1995) and the Sorority Member Scrapbooks (1930-1972), all sub-series of the Scrapbook Series. A tape recorded interview with Grace Maguire Swanner (1993) is located in the Subject Files Series.
Evidence of Psi Gamma Sorority's financial activities is located in the Psi Gamma Sorority Financial Records Series (1927-1991). Psi Gamma budget information is located in the budget files (1972-1976, 1993-1994), meeting minutes files (1955-1994) and the president's notes (1974-1983). Finally, fund-raising activities (1971-1982) are documented in the Subject Files Series.
Of particular note in this sub-group are the Greek workshops files (1963) that contain records documenting the controversy surrounding the Greek organization's move from an independently owned house to the dorm rooms on the main campus.
Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Records (1922-1997).
This sub group contains correspondence, minutes, newsletters, constitutions, membership lists, officer lists, surveys and questionnaires, certificates of incorporation, tax forms, bank statements, of the Psi Gamma Alumnae Association and copies of records created by the Pis Gamma Beta Chapter in Stony Brook, NY. Although the records date from 1922 though 1997, the bulk of the records were created between 1981 and 1995.
Records documenting routine administrative activities are located in the executive board meeting minutes (1922-1956) and the annual meeting minutes (1981-1995), both located in the Subject Files Series. The alumnae newsletters files (1952-1997) of the Subject Files Series also provide brief updates of the association's administrative activities. Documents establishing guidelines for the governance of the association include the constitution file (1924-1993) of the Subject Files Series and the exempt organization certificate (1994) of the Financial Records Series. Other records documenting the financial administration of the association are located in the monthly bank statements (1987-1990), and savings certificate passbook (1988-1995) in the Financial Records Series.
Information about the addresses, numbers, and activities of alumnae members is located in the alumnae newsletters files (1952-1997), membership lists (1922-1983), in the video recording of the 1994 annual meeting, all located in the Subject Files Series, and in the History Survey Series Questionnaires (1993-1994). The History Survey Series also provides detailed information about the education, honors, activities, interests, and recollections of former sorority members in the questionnaire responses files (1993-1994). The names of the first alumnae members from the Beta Chapter are located in the alumnae lists (1992-1995) of the Beta Chapter Files. Further information about alumnae can be found in the Anniversary Scrapbooks Sub-Series (1898-1995) and in the anniversary files (1963-1988) of the Psi Gamma Sorority Records Subject Files Series.
Records documenting the creation, administration, and activities sponsored by the Psi Gamma Sorority Beta Chapter are located in the executive board minutes (1991-1992), general meeting minutes (1992-1994), the president's report (1993-1994), and in the correspondence files (1991-1994) of the Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Beta Chapter Files. Further information about the Beta Chapter's creation and activities is located in the alumnae newsletters (1991-1997) in the Alumnae Association's Subject Files. Several Beta Chapter Alumnae also appear in the video cassette of the 1994 annual meeting.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Acquisition Information
The bulk of these records (1898-1997) were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Psi Gamma Alumnae Association Inc., in 1997. The records and ephemera had been housed by Mary Anne Lanni of the Alumnae Association since 1987.
Related Materials
Photographs related to Psi Gamma Sorority from the University Archives Photograph Collection are available for viewing online from the University at Albany Libraries' Digital Collections database.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
College sorority members; Greek letter societies; UAlbany Student Groups; State University of New York at Albany.
- Psi Gamma Sorority Records, 1989-1995; 1
  - Series 1: Psi Gamma Sorority Subject Files, 1898-1995; 1.1; 2 cubic ft.
    Scope and Contents
    This series consists of correspondence, minutes, reports, invitations, newspaper articles, constitutions and by-laws, brochures, directories, poems, workshops, evaluations, skit and music lyrics, questionnaires, newsletters, inventories, bills, receipts, contracts, and rush handbooks.
    The regular meeting minutes (1955-1994, missing 1972-1973, 1976-1981, and 1987-1988) are produced during regularly held meetings where general administrative topics, social events, fund-raisers are discussed. The president's notes files (1974-1983, missing 1979-1980) contain the personal agendas and notes of the sorority's president produced during these meetings. The rush files (1955-1993, missing academic years 1976-1977, 1978-1979, 1980-1982, 1983-1988, and 1989-1992), and anniversary celebrations files (1968, 1973, 1978, 1983, and 1988) contain announcements, attendance lists, and other ephemera produced during these regular events.
    Information collected during meetings and social events such as the membership lists folders (1933-1994, missing 1935-1941, 1944-1948, 1951-1958, 1960-1961, 1967-1973, 1977-1980, and 1987-1988), the sorority member directories (1898-1995), and the pledge Lists (1963, 1984-1994) all contain the names, addresses, and phone numbers of sorority members and pledges. The sorority's interactions with other Greek organizations is located in the panhellenic association rules and regulations (1988-1994), and the Greek workshops files (1963). Finally, the correspondence with alumnae files (1968-1990), the newsletters to the Alumnae Association from actives (1974-1977, 1981), the alumnae secretary report (1968-1971, 1977), and the tape recorded interview with Grace Maguire Swanner (1993) all contain records documenting the sorority's relationships with the Alumnae Association.
    See also newsletters to alumnae association by actives.
    Anniversary files include banquet announcements, sorority histories, and ephemera from banquets.
    Budget information also located in annual reports file.
    Arrangement
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Albany Student Press, 1966 March 29 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 1)
    - Albany Student Press, 1977 October 21 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 2)
    - Albany Student Press, 1979 March 17 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 3)
    - Alpha Advising Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 4)
    - Alumnae Secretary Report (Active), 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 5)
    - Alumnae Secretary Report (Active), 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 6)
    - Alumnae Secretary Report (Active), 1977 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 7)
    - Alumni Association: Present and Proposed Constitution, 1962 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 8)
    - Anniversary: 70th, 1968 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 9)
    - Anniversary: 75th, 1973 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 10)
    - Anniversary: 80th, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 11)
    - Anniversary: 85th, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 12)
    - Anniversary: 90th, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 13)
    - Anniversary: 100th, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 15)
      Include budgets, minutes, event calendars and announcements.
    - Applications for Appointed Offices, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 16)
    - Applications for Membership, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 17)
    - Applications for Edna Shafer MacAffer Award, 1983; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 18)
    - Appointed Positions List, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 19)
    - Attendance Register, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 20)
    - Bid Forms (Blank), Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 21)
    - Birthday Lists, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 22)
    - Budgets, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 23)
    - Budgets, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 24)
    - Brochures, 1981; 1991 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 25)
    - Carillon, 1982 February (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 26)
    - Carillon, 1987 Fall (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 27)
    - Carillon, 1987-1988 Winter (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 28)
    - Collegian, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 29)
    - Committee Lists, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 30)
    - Community Service, 1972-1986 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 31)
    - Conflict Party Bid Forms (Blank), 1972 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 32)
    - Constitutions, 1965-199? (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 33)
    - Correspondence with Alumnae, 1968-1990 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 34)
    - Dean's List, 1966 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 35)
    - Directories, 1898-1995 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 36)
      (Includes home addresses of sorority sisters).
    - "Desiderada" by Max Ehrman, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 37)
    - Executive Board Handbooks, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 38)
    - Faculty Advisors: Oath of Honorary Membership, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 39)
    - Faculty Members List, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 40)
    - Family Tree: From Sue Judge to Peggy Carol, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 41)
    - Family Tree: From Jane S. Benjamin '39 - Debbie White '90 (chart and 15 printed pages), Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 42)
    - Family Tree: From Molly Knight '57 to Margy Mays '67, donated by Linda Kroell '66, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 43)
    - Family Tree, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 44)
    - Formals, 1965-1969 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 45)
    - Fraternity Lists, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 46)
    - Fund-raising, 1971-1982 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 47)
    - Greek Constitutions, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 48)
    - Greek Evaluations, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 49)
    - Greek Week Participants, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 50)
    - Greek Workshops, 1963; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 51-52)
      Includes Dean Hartley's discussions with Greek representatives, new university policies concerning the regulation of fraternities and sororities, studies comparing cumulative grade point averages of Greek and non-Greek students, workshop invitations and schedules.
      See also student senate minutes.
    - Group Housing, 1970-1982 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 53)
    - Holiday Sing, 1967 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 54)
    - Inter-Fraternity Council/Panhel Relations, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 55)
    - Lounge Inventory, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 56)
    - Membership Certification of Beverly Caccavale, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 57)
    - Membership Lists, 1933-1934 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 58)
    - Membership Lists, 1942-1943 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 59)
    - Membership Lists, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 60)
    - Membership Lists, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 61)
    - Membership Lists, 1962-1966 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 62)
    - Membership Lists, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 63)
    - Membership Lists, 1981-1986 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 64)
    - Membership Lists, 1989-1994 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 65)
      See also mothers/daughters lists.
    - Merit/Demerit Book, Undated (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 66)
    - Merit/Demerit Tally, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 67)
    - Minutes: Executive Board, 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 68)
      Executive board and regular meeting minutes include agendas, schedules of events, financial records, and membership lists.
      See also president's notes, annual reports, and executive board handbooks.
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records))
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 69)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 70)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 71)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 72)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 73)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 74)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 75)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 76)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 77)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 78)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 79)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 5)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 6)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 12)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 13)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 14)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 17)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 18)
    - Minutes: Regular Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 19)
    - Mothers/Daughters Lists, 1981-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 20)
      See also membership lists.
    - Newsletters to Alumnae Association from Actives, 1974-1977; 1981 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 21)
      See also alumnae secretary reports.
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 22)
    - Oath of Cumulative Average, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 23)
    - Oaths of Office, 1908-1990 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 24)
    - Officers Lists, 1983-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 25)
    - Open House Cards (Blank), Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 26)
    - Panhellenic Association Rules and Regulations, 1988-1994 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 27)
    - Party Posters, Undated (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 28)
    - Phone Lists, 1988-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 29)
    - Pledge Invitations, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 30)
    - Pledge Book, ca. 1960 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 31)
    - Pledge Lists, 1963; 1984-1991 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 32)
      See also rush files.
    - President's Lists, 1898-1948 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 33)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1974-1975 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 34)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1975-1976 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 35)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1976-1977 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 36)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1977-1978 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 37)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1981-1982 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 38)
    - President's Notes (Psi Gam), 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Psi Gamma Sorority Records), Folder 39)
      See also executive board minutes, regular meeting minutes, and executive board handbook.